

## **Dorian-Ioan VELICI**

O Home: Spl. 1 Decembrie 1918, bl. 29, ap. 16, 305500, Lugoj, Romania

Email: dorian.ioan\_velici@hotmail.com Phone: (+40) 720390573

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dorian-ioan-velici/

Gender: Male Date of birth: 15/12/1996 Place of birth: Lugoj, Romania Nationality: Romanian

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a problem-solving person. Both in my personal & professional space, I particularly enjoy using my skills to solve challenging problems, to future improve processes and to prevent less desired outcomes from occurring.

By working at FORVIA Hella Lugoj as a Technical Assistant in the Backend Area, I gained on-field demonstrated experience, developed my general knowledge and analytical skills around PCBtesting equipment, CNC routing machines & automatic soldering stations by configuring / maintaining the equipment, optimizing / redesigning the programs and, finally - improving the overall manufacturing processes when needed.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

[ 01/10/2017 - 01/07/2021 ]

## **Information Technology Engineer**

"Ioan Slavici" University - Faculty of Engineering

City: Timișoara | Country: Romania

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### [11/10/2024 - Current] Website Developer

City: Lugoj | Country: Romania

Website development - both programming & designing web pages in my spare time.

[ 27/04/2023 – Current ]

# **Technical Assistant (Backend Area)**

FORVIA Hella https://www.hella.com/hella-ro/

City: Lugoj | Country: Romania | Email address: dorianioan.velici@forvia.com | Name of unit or department: PCB Production (Backend Area) | Business or sector: Manufacturing

My usual tasks consist in:

- regular analytical & problem-solving activities;
- technical maintenance and equipment repair;
- program optimization / redesign for many essential devices used at PCB-manufacturing processes.

The equipment I'm most familiar with:

- ICT/EOL teststands (Aeroflex 4250 & National Instruments NI LabVIEW), Takaya Flying Probe
- automatic selective soldering machines (SEHO SelectLine C systems);
- CNC routing machines used in the PCB depaneling process (Schunk & Asys Divisio 2000 Ergo millings);
- Maestro 4S cutting stations;
- plus other PCB-manufacturing factory equipment.

# [ 02/06/2015 - Current ] **IT Technician**

City: Lugoj | Country: Romania

In my spare time I also:

- Configure, upgrade & optimize Windows OS-based systems;
- Troubleshoot & fix hardware failures:

- Improve the overall performance, gain stability & fix problems caused by software-related issues.

# **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Romanian

Other language(s):

**English** 

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2** 

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

# **DRIVING LICENCE**

Motorbikes: AM B

### **SKILLS**

NI LabVIEW | Computer Literacy | PCB Debugging | Process Optimization | CNC Programming | Process Failure Mode Effects Analysis | Website Development